in this lecture we'll make a chain icon
在这节课中，我们将制作一个链式图标
using the shape Builder tool I right
使用Shape Builder工具I右
click on the canvas and choose document
在画布上单击，然后选择文档
properties behind orientation I click on
我点击了方向背后的属性
landscape to rotate the document 90
横向旋转文档90
degrees
学位
I click on the rectangle tool and drag a
我单击矩形工具，然后将一个
rectangle I will hide The Stroke by
矩形我将隐藏笔划
shift-clicking on the Red Cross
按住Shift键并单击红十字会
around the corners to create a hole
绕过拐角，形成一个洞
let's try duplicating the rectangle I
让我们试着把这个矩形复制到
make the duplicate green I press shift
按Shift键将复制件变为绿色
plus control and make the rectangle
加上控件，并使矩形
smaller we see the green rectangle
我们看到较小的绿色矩形
doesn't scale proportionally so I press
没有按比例扩展，所以我按下
Ctrl set to undo let's try and setting I
将Ctrl设置为撤消让我们尝试并设置
press Ctrl 9 a couple of times at first
首先按几次Ctrl 9
glance this looks okay
扫一眼，这看起来还行
so I will select them both and go to
因此，我将同时选择它们并转到
path difference now I go to view display
路径差异现在转到查看显示
mode outline notice that I assigned
我分配的模式大纲通知
control y to toggle between normal and
控制y在正常和正常之间切换
outline mode as it is in illustrator we
在Illustrator WE中的轮廓模式
will look at shortcuts in a later
我将在稍后的
lecture when I click on the Node tool I
当我单击Node Tool I时讲课
see the nodes of the inset path are a
请看，插入路径的节点是
bit off to get a perfect path let's try
为得到一条完美的道路而努力让我们试一试
something else I press Ctrl Y and
我按下Ctrl Y并执行其他操作
control Z I delete the green rectangle I
控件Z I删除绿色矩形I
give the rectangle a stroke and increase
给矩形一个笔划，并增加
its width I set the fill to none if I
其宽度我将填充设置为无，如果
press Ctrl y we see we just have a
按Ctrl键我们看到我们只有一个
single line I go to path stroke to path
单行我转到路径笔划到路径
it looks like nothing happened
看起来好像什么都没发生
but when I press Ctrl y we see I have
但当我按下Ctrl y时，我们看到我有
outlined The Stroke of the path if I
勾勒出了路径的笔触
click on the Node tool and click on the
单击节点工具，然后单击
path we see the nodes are now perfect
我们看到的路径节点现在是完美的
now that I have changed the stroke to a
现在我已经将笔划更改为
fill I will fill it with orange I
我会把它装满橙色的
duplicate the chain element and make it
复制链元素并使其成为
green
绿色
I select snapping and drag until it
我选择捕捉并拖动，直到它
snaps I select both elements and click
捕捉我选择了两个元素，然后单击
on the shape Builder tool when I drag I
当我拖动时在形状生成器工具上
see I get an unwanted connection
看，我得到了一个不想要的连接
so I press on the X and go to path
所以我按下X键并转到Path
fracture
骨折
I click on the shape Builder tool again
我再次单击Shape Builder工具
I keep my mouse pressed down and drag to
我按住鼠标并将其拖动到
connect some parts of the right chain
连接正确链条的一些部分
then I let go of the mouse now I also
然后我放开鼠标现在我也
drag over parts of the other chain I
我拖着另一条链条的一部分
click on finish
单击finish
like in illustrator you sometimes have
就像插画家你有时会有的那样
to do a little cleaning up I click on
要做一些清理，我点击
the Node tool and look for nodes that
节点工具并查找
are Superfluous if there are any I
如果有我的话，我就是超级的
select them and press delete I will give
选择它们并按删除键，我会给出
the chain a stroke and I remove the fill
链条一划，我去掉填充物
when I scale the icon I see the stroke
当我缩放图标时，我看到笔画
doesn't scale with it the reason is that
无法与之相适应，原因是
proportional stroke scaling is not
比例中风比例不是
selected which normally is what I want
选择通常是我想要的
when I select it the stroke scales
当我选择它时，笔画量表
proportionally with the scaling the best
比例与比例最好
solution however is to outline the
然而，解决方案是概述
stroke as we did before regardless
无论如何，就像我们以前那样中风
whether stroke scaling is activated the
是否激活中风量表
chain can now be scaled to any size
链现在可以扩展到任何尺寸